[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which part of th eye captures light rays and converts the rays into electrical impulses?", "correct_answer": "Retina", "incorrect_answers": ["Iris", "Cornea", "Pupil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This former SNL comic and 61* director was the voice of the one-eyed creature Mike Wazowski.", "correct_answer": "Billy Crystal", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim Carrey", "Robin Williams", "Damen Wayans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 650BC the father of medicine, Hippocrates, recommended it to relieve stomach pain.", "correct_answer": "Linseed", "incorrect_answers": ["Soy", "None of these", "Oatmeal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In casinos where Blackjack dealers must hit on soft 17 the game is substantially more favorable for the player than in casinos where dealers must stand on soft 17.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These are lumps of ice and dust.  When they get close enough to the Sun they gradually evaporate.  Jets of gas and dust create long tails that people can see from Earth.", "correct_answer": "Comets", "incorrect_answers": ["Asteroids", "UFOs", "Stars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is one day on the planet Jupiter?", "correct_answer": "Just under 10 hours", "incorrect_answers": ["Just over 12 hours", "24 hours", "55 hours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the lucky winner of the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actor for 1994.", "correct_answer": "Kevin Costner for Wyatt Earp", "incorrect_answers": ["Steven Seagal for On Deadly Ground", "All of these", "Sylvester Stallone for The Specialist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jason Bournes girlfriend from the first two Bourne movies starring Matt Damon, does not appear in The Bourne Ultimatum.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hijab, which is also a term meaning barrier, is worn as a traditional clothing in which countries?", "correct_answer": "Arabic", "incorrect_answers": ["African", "European", "Latin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the film Over Her Dead Body?", "correct_answer": "Jeff Lowell", "incorrect_answers": ["Judd Apatow", "James Benning", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first bridge in what would become the USA was built in this state.", "correct_answer": "Massachusetts", "incorrect_answers": ["New Jersey", "Pennsylvania", "Virginia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What distinctive anatomical feature does the beetle species Trogodendron fasciculatum possess?", "correct_answer": "Bright yellow antennae", "incorrect_answers": ["A green W mark on the back", "Very large red eyes", "Its abdomen is blue"]}]